Inventory of the American Institutes for Research reports
Hoover Institution Archives
- General Topics File
  - 22300. Coordination and evaluation of videodisc and microcomputer programs
    - Final technical report, 1983 December
  - 25900. Development of the National Assessment of Educational Progress
    - Final report, 1982 November; 2 copies
  - 26500. Issues for the development of reading and writing software
    - Technical report, 1983 January
  - 31400. Research on the use of technology in the education of the learning disabled. Project CREATE
    - Final report, 1987 December
- Project TALENT File
  Although the contents of this box represent the major publications from Project TALENT, it is not a comprehensive collection. Other TALENT publications not included here can be borrowed via inter-library loan from American Institutes for Research, Palo Alto.
  - Project TALENT Specimen Set of Materials, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Design for a Study of American Youth, Houghton-Mifflin, 1962
  - Studies of the American High School, Project TALENT, 1962
  - Studies of a Complete Age Group: Age 15, American Institutes for Research, 1963 (Box 48)
  - The American High School Student, American Institutes for Research, 1964
  - Project TALENT One-Year Follow-up Studies, Project TALENT, 1966
  - The High School Years: Growth in Cognitive Skills, American Institutes for Research, 1967
  - Interpreting Canonical Correlations: Theory and Practice, American Institutes for Research, 1968
  - Five Years After High School, American Institutes for Research, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Five Years After High School: Appendix II, American Institutes for Research, 1971
  - The Career Data Book: Results from Project TALENT's Five Year Follow-up Study, American Institutes for Research, 1973
  - An Empirical Study to Aid in Formulating Educational Goals, American Institutes for Research, 1975
  - Using the TALENT Profiles in Counseling: A Supplement to the Career Data Book, American Institutes for Research, 1975
  - Methodology of the Project TALENT 11-year Follow-up Study, American Institutes for Research, 1976 (Box 50)
  - The American Citizen: 11 Years after High School, Volume I, American Institutes for Research, 1975
  - The American Citizen: 11 Years after High School, Volume II, American Institutes for Research, 1977
  - Designing a Study of Adult Accomplishment and Life Quality: A Report on Phase I of the Project TALENT 17-year Follow-up Survey and TALENT Data Bank Maintenance Activities, American Institutes for Research, 1977
  - An Exploratory Study of Barriers to Usage of Large-scale Data Bases such as Project TALENT, American Institutes for Research, 1977
  - The Project TALENT Data Bank Handbook, American Institutes for Research, 1979
  - Origins and Career Consequences of Sex Differences in High School Mathematics Achievement, American Institutes for Research, 1979